Community Cookbook Collection: Local Organization Non-Profit Cookbooks and Nationally-Published Popular Cookbooks, 1907-2008 TX614.C66
Lilly Library
- NATIONAL
  - 4. The Meats Cookbook: Southern Living; Progressive Farmer (Box Box 11)
    - Spine Title: The Meats Cookbook. Title: The Meats Cookbook. Description: By Southern Living. "The Darry's, 1972"-front cover. Nashville, TN: Favorite Recipes Press, 1971. [2], 3-192 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 5. Midwestern Junior League (Box Box 11)
    - Spine Title: The Midwestern Junior League Cookbook. Title: The Midwestern Junior League Cookbook. Description: Recipes from Junior Leagues across the Midwest, 1954-1978. 622 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 6. Memories of a Midwestern Farm: Good Food and Inspiration from Around the Kitchen Table (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: Memories of a Midwestern Farm: Good Food and Inspiration from Around the Kitchen Table. Spine Title: Memories of a Midwestern Farm. Title: Memories of a Midwestern Farm: Good Food and Inspiration from Around the Kitchen Table. Description: Illustrated by Richard Lang Chandler. New York, NY: Pocket Books, 1995. [11], 2-179 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in tan boards, with dj. (Box Box 11)
  - 7. My Own Cook Book: From Stillmeadow and Cape Cod (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: My Own Cook Book: From Stillmeadow and Cape Cod. Spine Title: My Own Cookbook. Title: My Own Cook Book: From Stillmeadow and Cape Cod. Description: By Gladys Taber, with drawings by Pamela Johnson. Orleans, MA: Parnassus Imprints, 1972. [10], 11-312 p.: ill., index, notes; 23 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 11)
  - 8. Nell Nichols Reports: Good Home Cooking across the U.S.A. (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: Nell Nichols Reports: Good Home Cooking across the U.S.A. Spine Title: Good Home Cooking across the U.S.A. Title: Nell Nichols Reports... Good Home Cooking across the U.S.A. Description: By Nell B. Nichols, with illustrations by Ray Irwin. Ames, IA: The Iowa State College Press, 1952. [18], 3-619 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Bound in blue boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 9. The Norman Rockwell Illustrated Cookbook: Classic American Recipes (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: The Norman Rockwell Illustrated Cookbook: Classic American Recipes. Spine Title: The Norman Rockwell Illustrated Cookbook. Title: The Norman Rockwell Illustrated Cookbook: Classic American Recipes. Description: By George Mendoza. New York, NY: McGraw-Hill, 1987. [2], 5-126 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 10. North Carolina and Old Salem Cookery (Box Box 11)
    - Description: By Elizabeth Hedgecock Sparks (Beth Tartan). Kernersville, NC, 1955. [13], 2-226 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in red boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 11. The Old-Time Brand-Name Cookbook: Recipes, Illustrations, and Advice from the Early Kitchens of America's Most Trusted Food Makers (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: The Old-Time Brand-Name Cookbook: Recipes, Illustrations, and Advice from the Early Kitchens of America's Most Trusted Food Makers. Spine Title: The Old-Time Brand-Name Cookbook. Title: The Old-Time Brand-Name Cookbook: Recipes, Illustrations, and Advice from the Early Kitchens of America's Most Trusted Food Makers. Description: By Bunny Crumpacker. New York, NY: Smithmark Publishers, 1998. [39] 4-123 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in tan illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 11)
  - 12. A Place Called Sweet Apple: Country Living and Southern Recipes (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: A Place Called Sweet Apple: Country Living and Southern Recipes. Spine Title: A Place Called Sweet Apple. Title: A Place Called Sweet Apple. Description: By Celestine Sibley. Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Co., Inc., 1973. [11], 12-240 p.: ill., index; 21 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 11)
  - 13. The Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese Cookbook (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: The Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese Cookbook. Spine Title: Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese Cookbook. Title: The Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese Cookbook. Description: Kraft, Inc., 1981. [2], 3-191 p.: ill., index; 21 cm. Spiral bound, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 14. The Prudhomme Family Cookbook: Old-Time Louisiana Recipes (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: The Prudhomme Family Cookbook: Old-Time Louisiana Recipes By the eleven Prudhomme brothers and sisters and Chef Paul Prudhomme. Spine Title: The Prudhomme Family Cookbook. Title: The Prudhomme Family Cookbook: Old-Time Louisiana Recipes by the eleven Prudhomme brothers and sisters and Chef Paul Prudhomme. Description: By the eleven Prudhomme brothers and sisters and Chef Paul Prudhomme. New York, NY: William Morrow and Company, INC., 1987. [20], 1-446 p.: index; 25 cm. Bound in white boards, with dj. (Box Box 11)
  - 15. Psi Iota Xi (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: Psi Iota Xi Cook Book. Description: Edited by Thelma Shanks. 72 p.: 22 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 11)
  - 1. Recipes and Memories from Mama Cash's Kitchen (Box Box 12)
    - Description: By Carrie Cash. Signed by author. [1], 2-6 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White wire spiral binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 12)
  - 2. Recipes from America's Restored Villages (Box Box 12)
    - Description: By Jean Anderson, with illustrations by Martin Silverman. Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1975. [29], 6-356 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Bound in red boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 3. Rumford Cook Book (Box Box 12)
    - Title: The Rumford Cook Book. Description: By Fannie Merritt Farmer, principal of the Boston Cooking School. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works. Foxing. [2], 3-47 p.: ill.,; 18 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 12)
  - 4. Rush Hour Dinners: Easy and Delicious Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Good Housekeeping: Rush Hour Dinners: Easy and Delicious Recipes. Spine Title: Good Housekeeping: Rush Hour Dinners. Title: Good Housekeeping: Rush Hour Dinners. Description: By Good Housekeeping. New York, NY: Hearst Books, 2005. [3], 4-32 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 5. Some Favorite Southern Recipes of the Duchess of Windsor (Box Box 12)
    - Description: With a foreword by the Duchess of Windsor. New York, NY: Gramercy Publishing Co., 1942. [18], 9-180 p.: index; 21 cm. Bound in blue boards, with dj. (Box Box 12)
  - 6. Southern Living: Annual Recipes Master Index, 1979-1992 (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title:Southern Living: Annual Recipes Master Index, 1979-1992. Spine Title: Annual Recipes Master Index, 1979-1992. Title: Southern Living: Annual Recipes Master Index, 1979-1992. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1993. [3], 4-176 p.: 28 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 12)
  - 7. Southern Living: 1980 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1980 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1980 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1980 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1980. [11], 2-341 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 8. Southern Living: 1981 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1981 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1981 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1981 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1981. [11], 2-340 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 9. Southern Living: 1983 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1983 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1983 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1983 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1983. [11], 2-357 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 10. Southern Living: 1984 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1984 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1984 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1984 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1984. [11], 2-373 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 11. Southern Living: 1985 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1985 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1985 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1985 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1985. [11], 2-373 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 12. Southern Living: 1986 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1986 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1986 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1986 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1986. [11], 2-373 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 13. Southern Living: 1987 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1987 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1987 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1987 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1987. [11], 2-342 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 14. Southern Living: 1988 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1988 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1988 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1988 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1988. [13], 2-340 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 15. Southern Living: 1990 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1990 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1990 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1990 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1990. [7], 8-360 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 16. Southern Living: 1992 Annual Recipes (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Southern Living: 1992 Annual Recipes. Spine Title: 1992 Southern Living Annual Recipes. Title: Southern Living: 1992 Annual Recipes. Description: Birmingham, Alabama: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1992. [7], 8-368 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 12)
  - 17. Spoonbread and Strawberry Wine (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Spoonbread and Strawberry Wine. Spine Title: Spoonbread and Strawberry Wine. Title: Spoonbread and Strawberry Wine: Recipes and Reminiscences of a Family. Description: By Norma Jean and Carole Darden. New York, NY: Fawcett Crest Books, 1980. [14], 15-288 p.: ill., index; 18 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 12)
  - 18. Stillmeadow Cook Book (Box Box 12)
    - Cover Title: Stillmeadow Cook Book. Spine Title: Stillmeadow Cook Book. Title: Gladys Taber's Stillmeadow Cook Book. Description: By Gladys Taber, with drawings by Ann Grifalconi. Orleans, MA: Parnassus Imprints, Inc., 1983. [8], 9-335 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 12)
  - 1. The Sunset Cook Book: Food with a Gourmet Touch (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: The Sunset Cook Book: Food with a Gourmet Touch. Spine Title: The Sunset Cook Book. Title: The Sunset Cook Book: Food with a Gourmet Touch. Description: By the Sunset Editorial Staff. Menlo Park, CA: Lane Book Compnay, 1960. [6], 7- 216 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 13)
  - 2. Thoughts for Buffets, copy 1 (Box Box 13)
    - Description: Decorations by William Barss. Book Club ed. Boston, MA: Houghton Mifflin Company Boston, 1958. [6], 1-425 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Bound in yellow boards, with dust jacket. (Box Box 13)
  - 3. Thoughts for Buffets, copy 2 (Box Box 13)
    - Description: Decorations by William Barss. Boston, MA: Houghton Mifflin Company Boston, 1958. [6], 1-425 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Bound in yellow boards. (Box Box 13)
  - 4. A Treasury of Great Recipes (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: A Treasury of Great Recipes. Spine Title: A Treasury of Great Recipes. Title: A Treasury of Great Recipes by Mary and Vincent Price: Famous Specialties of the World's Foremost Restaurants Adapted for the American Kitchen. Description: By Mary and Vincent Price. Signed by the author, "For June, My best and Bon appetite, Vincent Price." New York, NY: Grosset & Dunlap Publishers, 1974. [20], 21-488 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in gold metallic boards. (Box Box 13)
  - 5. Trinity Broadcasting Network (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: Caylan Recommends TBN Family Favorite Recipes. Spine Title: Caylan Recommends TBN Family Favorite Recipes. Title: Caylan Recommends TBN Family Favorite Recipes. Description: Recipes from the Crouch family. Santa Ana, California, 1993. "Printed in the United States of America"-from title page verso. 268 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 13)
  - 6. The White Cross Guild (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: The White Cross Guild, 1976-1977: A Book of Favorite Recipes. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes. Description: 1976-1977. 124 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 13)
  - 7. White House Cook Book (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: White House Cook Book. Spine Title: White House Cook Book. Title: The White House Cook Book: A Comprehensive Cyclopedia of Information for the Home, containing Cooking, Toilet, and Household Recipes, Menus, Dinner-Giving, Table Etiquette, Care of the Sick, Health Suggestions, Facts worth knowing, etc. Description: By Stella May Lowe. "Mrs. P"-page [1]. Includes handwritten recipes and notes. Akron, OH: The Saalfield Publishing Company, 1907. [12], 7-590 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in white boards. (Box Box 13)
  - 8. Whistler's Mother's Cook Book (Box Box 13)
    - Description: Edited by Margaret MacDonald. Contains thank you letter from Andy and Lynn Serafin to June and Mac McGlassen. New York, NY: G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1979. [6], 7-144 p.: ill., index; 16 cm. Bound in brown boards, with dj. (Box Box 13)
  - 9. Woman's Day Collector's Cook Book (Box Box 13)
    - Description: Introductions by James Beard and illustrated by Joseph Low. New York, NY: E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc., 1960. [6], 7-320 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Bound in yellow boards. (Box Box 13)
  - 10. WQED Pittsburgh (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: America's Home Cooking. Title: America's Home Cooking: Comfort Food: A production of WQED Pittsburgh. Description: "Comfort food" recipes from across the United States. 145 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black spiral binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 13)
  - 11. Blank Recipe Book (Box Box 13)
    - Cover Title: Recipes. Description: Empty recipe binder, with blank recipe cards, blank note cards, labeled and tabbed sections, photo slots. Ring binder, 25 cm. (Box Box 13)